U.S. Railroad Labor Board Proceedings and Related Documents 5327
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Railroad Labor Board Proceedings and Related Documents
1921
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Department of Labor
5327
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents).
US Railroad Labor Board publications.
8214632
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 28, 2014
EAD encoding:
Elizabeth Parker, October 16, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5366: American Federation of Labor, Railway Employees Department vs. Union Pacific Railroad Company, Hanson et al. Records 5291m: Amtrak Records 5188 AV: Association of American Railroads "Railroad Regulation: An Absurd Game" Slide Transparencies and Sound Recording 5188m: Association of American Railroads Agreement of May 1936 5989 mf: Blacks in the Railroad Industry on Microfilm 5475: Brotherhood of Locomotive Firemen and Enginemen General Chairman, Boston and Maine Railroad Records 5347: Brotherhood of Maintenance of Way Employees, ICC, and Erie Lackawanna Briefs Regarding the Railroad Merger 5030 MB: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Memorabilia 5182 P: Brotherhood of Railroad Signalmen of America Photographs 5894: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Railroad Booklets 5021: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Additional Records 6312m: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Annual Report of the Legislative Board 5631: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad General Committee File 5647: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Joppa Lodge (Toledo, OH) Minute Books 5446: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Ledger 5623: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Legislative Board of New York Files 5149 MB: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Memorabilia 5612: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Moosic Tunnel Lodge no.93 Meeting Minutes 5149 P: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 5149: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5080: Chicago and Western Indiana Railroad Company et al. and Railroad Brotherhoods Arbitration Proceedings 5943: Dan A. Ballard Collection of Railroad Memorabilia & Wage Information 5153m: Dedham Branch Railroad Pay Roll 5514: Earnings of Train and Engine Service Employees Reports 5183: Edward Heisler Collection of Southern Pacific Railroad Operating Crafts Union Organizing Documents 5102: Emergency Board No. 129, Long Island Railroad and the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, Locals 517 and 1090, Records 5496 mf: George Novack "Unity Caucus on the Railroads: The Story of the Consolidation Committee of Enginemen" on Microfilm 5295: Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Company Selected Personnel Files 5197 MB: Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Memorabilia 5197: Illinois Central Gulf Railroad Miscellany 5557: In the Matter of the PRR Merger with NYC Railroad Company Finance Dockett #'s 21989, 21990 Minutes 5449 mf: J. F. Miller "Report to Joseph Wood, General Manager, Pennsylvania Lines West of Pittsburgh, on the 1894 Strike of the American Railroad Union" (222 p) on Microfilm 5759 AV: John F. Kennedy Presidential Recordings regarding Railroad Work Rules Dispute 6268 P: Joint Committee of Adjustment for the Rock Island System's Order of Railway Conductors and Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photograph 6312 P: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Photographs 6312 PUBS: Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Publications
Bernard and Reis Company; United States. b Railroad Retirement Board; United States. Railroad Retirement Board
8214632
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 845. Volume 1, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  October 26 1921
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 353. Volume 11, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  June 6 - 8 1921
- US railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 353. Volume 14, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  May 5 - June 9 1921
- University of North Carolina. The Enforcement of Railroad Labor Board Decisions, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  November 1 1922
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 2906. Volume 11, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  May 26 1924
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 2906. Volume 11, 1924 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  May 26 1924.
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 2906, 1922-1925 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  Two volumes. December 21 1922 - October 21 1925
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 2906, 1924-1925 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  Three volumes. April 16 1924 - October 21 1925.
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 2906, 1922 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  December 21 1922
- US Railroad Labor Board. Docket No. 4796, 1925 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  October 21 1925
- US Railroad Labor Board. Dockets 1-2-3. Rules and Working Conditions. Volume 1, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  April 18 1921
- US Railroad Labor Board. Dockets 1-2-3. Rules and Working Conditions. Volume 1, 1921 (Box 1, Folder 12)